ALPER CUBUKCU

Mid-Level Software Developer

CONTACT

+61 452 563 876
alpercubukcuu@gmail.com
www.linkedin.com/in/alpercubukcu/
github.com/alpercubukcuu
Sydney NSW 2200

SUMMARY

As an experienced Full-Stack Developer, I have gained in-depth expertise in software projects over the last 3 years, with a particular focus on backend development. With my solution-oriented approach and technical skills, I have played a key role in improving the efficiency of teams and product quality.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Ahmet Yesevi University 2020 - 2023 - GPA: 3.21

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: C#, Javascript, TypeScript
- Frameworks & Libraries:
 .NET,WPF, React, jQuery, Ajax
- Web Technologies: HTML,
 CSS ,Bootstrap, UIKit
- Database & Caching: Postgre SQL, MySQL, MS-SQL, Redis
- DevOps & Cloud: Docker,
 MicroService, Azure,
 Kuberetes, AWS
- Version Control: Git, Jenkins
- Project Management: Jira,
 Agile Methodology, Sprint &
 Scrum

LICENCES AND CERTIFICATES

University of California: SQL for

Data Science. Link

Amazon Web Services (AWS):

Building Modern .NET Applications on AWS. Link

WORK EXPERIENCE

MID-LEVEL DEVELOPER

Nexum

www.nexum.com.tr/en

Jan 2023 - Present

Our company, known for hundreds of B2B, B2C and B2E projects since 2000, is a pioneer in .NET technologies as a Microsoft Gold Development Partner. I played a central role in the infrastructure development of Pegasus, one of Turkey's major airlines. Technologies utilised;

 .NET 7, C#, CQRS, MediatR, Powershell, JWT, Azure, ReactJS, Gulp, Redis, MSSQL and OData.

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Webbilir

www.webbilir.com

July 2021 - Jan 2023

More than 1000 customers have served web application and mobile application solutions in Webbilir company.

I carried out the software works of FAKIR company, which is based in Germany and has a large market for technological household appliances in Turkey. Technologies utilised;

 .Net 3.1, WPF, C#, Onion Architecture, Repository Pattern, Unit Of Work, Rest API, MSSQL, Powershell, Jquery, Ajax, Html, Css, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Ulkit.

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

WorkinTeam workinteam.net, indianic.com

Jan 2021 - July 2021

Workinteam, the partner of IndiaNIC software company in Turkey, is a company that produces all kinds of digital solutions. Technologies utilised; PHP, Html, CSS, Javascript